<?xml version="1.0"?>

<rss version="2.0">

<channel>

<title>TRAIN Conference</title>
<link>http://www.trainconference.com</link>
<description>
  TRAIN Conference (Calgary, Alberta, Canada) offers seminars and resources to
  equip and encourage Christian Education workers in their ministry areas.
</description>
<category>Christian conferences</category>
<image>
  <url>http://www.trainconference.com/logoRSS.gif</url>
  <title>TRAIN -- encouraging, equipping</title>
  <link>http://www.trainconference.com</link>
  <width>144</width>
  <height>59</height>
</image>
<language>en-us</language>

<item>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">20060910A</guid>
  <title>TRAIN 2006 Conference (November 3-4) -- Body Building</title>
  <link>http://www.trainconference.com/</link>
  <category>Christian conferences</category>
  <pubDate>Sun, 10 Sep 2006 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
  <description>
    Engage in a TRAIN workout designed to shape up Christian Education leaders
    and workers in Christ's Body.  Exercise any of these ministry muscle
    groups:  children, youth, family, women, small groups, leadership and
    compassion.  TRAIN is for the encouraging and equipping of Adult Ministry
    Leaders, Bible Study Leaders, Small Group Leaders, Apprentices and Coaches,
    Sunday School Teachers (all age levels), Children's Ministry Leaders -
    Pastors, Directors and Workers, Youth Ministry Leaders - Pastors, Workers
    and Sponsors, Young Adult Ministry Leaders, Women's Ministry Leaders, and
    Compassion Ministry Leaders.
  </description>
</item>

<item>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">20060910B</guid>
  <title>Conference Information</title>
  <link>http://www.trainconference.com/conference.html</link>
  <category>Christian conferences</category>
  <pubDate>Sun, 10 Sep 2006 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
  <description>
    The TRAIN 2006 Conference will be held at Grace Baptist Church -- 2670
    Radcliffe Dr. SE, Calgary, AB, CANADA.  Two new tracks this year are
    "Curriculum" and "Family Ministries".  Check out the many new seminars
    offered this year, as well as a few well-received repeats from last year --
    all designed to equip you with relevant and fresh ideas for your ministry.
  </description>
</item>

<item>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">20060910C</guid>
  <title>Guest Speaker:  Lou Leventhal -- "Illusions &amp; Reality"</title>
  <link>http://www.trainconference.com/conference.html#speaker</link>
  <category>Christian conferences</category>
  <pubDate>Sun, 10 Sep 2006 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
  <description>
    Internationally acclaimed Illusionist Lou Leventhal will present his fun
    and highly entertaining program, "Illusions &amp; Reality," on Friday,
    November 3 at 7:30pm.  Unbelievable stage illusions, live animals, audience
    participation, original music, infectious humour and inspiring spiritual
    truths are orchestrated into an exciting and fast-paced show that you won't
    want to miss.
  </description>
</item>

<item>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">20060910D</guid>
  <title>Registration Information"</title>
  <link>http://www.trainconference.com/registration.html</link>
  <category>Christian conferences</category>
  <pubDate>Sun, 10 Sep 2006 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
  <description>
    There are three ways to register for the TRAIN 2006 Conference:  online
    (recommended), mail-in and walk-in.  Tickets for just Lou Leventhal's
    Illusions &amp; Reality on Friday night are also available.  A list of
    hotels near the conference site is provided for convenience.
  </description>
</item>

<item>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">20060910E</guid>
  <title>Exhibitors and Attending Churches</title>
  <link>http://www.trainconference.com/webLinks.html</link>
  <category>Christian conferences</category>
  <pubDate>Sun, 10 Sep 2006 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
  <description>
    These are some of the exhibitors you'll see at the TRAIN 2006 Conference:
    Alberta Bible College, Alliance University College, AWANA, BCM
    International, Christian Publications, FaithLife Financial, Heart of a
    Child, Noonday Ventures, Pioneer Clubs, and Talbot Marketing.
  </description>
</item>

<item>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">20060910F</guid>
  <title>Privacy Policy</title>
  <link>http://www.trainconference.com/privacyPolicy.html</link>
  <category>Christian conferences</category>
  <pubDate>Sun, 10 Sep 2006 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
  <description>
    Our privacy policy states what information we collect and what we do with
    it.  We DON'T share any personally-identifiable information with any third
    parties.  Also, individuals, churches and organizations are reminded that
    they may opt-in or opt-out of our mailing list at any time.
  </description>
</item>

<item>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">20060910G</guid>
  <title>Who We Are</title>
  <link>http://www.trainconference.com/whoWeAre.html</link>
  <category>Christian conferences</category>
  <pubDate>Sun, 10 Sep 2006 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
  <description>
    The first TRAIN Conference was held in 1983.  Every year since, as the
    baton is passed on to new committe members, we hope that we will be able to
    encourage, train, provide purpose-filled resources and develop Christian
    workers and leaders.  Contact us if you have any questions or comments, or
    if you are interested in volunteering with us in the future.
  </description>
</item>

<item>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">20061025A</guid>
  <title>Plenty of Space Still Available</title>
  <link>http://www.trainconference.com/</link>
  <category>Christian conferences</category>
  <pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2006 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
  <description>
    As of 2006/10/24, everyone who has registered for the conference so far is
    guarenteed admission to Lou Leventhal's show, and there are plenty of
    tickets still available.
  </description>
</item>

<item>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">20061102A</guid>
  <title>Not Registered Yet?  Walk-Ins Welcome!</title>
  <link>http://www.trainconference.com/</link>
  <category>Christian conferences</category>
  <pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2006 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
  <description>
    Online registration is now closed.  As of 2006/11/01, everyone who has
    registered for the conference so far is guarenteed admission to Lou
    Leventhal's show, and there are plenty of tickets still available.  If
    you'd still like to register for the conference then please print off a
    paper registration form, fill it in and bring it with you on Friday night.
  </description>
</item>

<item>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">20061106A</guid>
  <title>The TRAIN 2006 Conference is Over</title>
  <link>http://www.trainconference.com/</link>
  <category>Christian conferences</category>
  <pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2006 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
  <description>
    The TRAIN 2005 Conference is now over.  We trust and pray that you found
    encouragement in the Lord, and that you will continue to build up the body
    of Christ in your ministry area.
  </description>
</item>

</channel>

</rss>