<?xml version="1.0"?>

<rss version="2.0">

<channel>

<title>TRAIN Conference</title>
<link>http://www.trainconference.com</link>
<description>
  TRAIN Conference (Calgary, Alberta, Canada) offers seminars and resources to
  equip and encourage Christian Education workers in their ministry areas.
</description>
<image>
  <url>http://www.trainconference.com/logoRSS.gif</url>
  <title>TRAIN -- encouraging, equipping</title>
  <link>http://www.trainconference.com</link>
  <width>144</width>
  <height>59</height>
</image>
<language>en-us</language>

<item>
  <title>
    Exhibitors and Attending Churches
  </title>
  <link>http://www.trainconference.com/webLinks.html</link>
  <category>Christian conferences</category>
  <pubDate>Thu, 04 Aug 2005 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
  <description>
    Exhibitors have begun requesting space at the TRAIN 2005 Conference.
    Churches are starting to indicate their forthcoming participation in the
    conference, too.  If your church is also planning on sending people then
    let us know and we'll be happy to add a hyperlink its website.
  </description>
</item>

<item>
  <title>
    Conference Information
  </title>
  <link>http://www.trainconference.com/conference.html</link>
  <category>Christian conferences</category>
  <pubDate>Sun, 31 Aug 2005 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
  <description>
    Details about the TRAIN 2005 Conference are now available.  Our keynote
    speaker will be Randy Carter of Straight Talk Ministries.  The Resource
    Centre will include displays &amp; exhibits from a variety of publishers,
    including Cook Communications, Gospel Light, Group, Standard Publishing and
    Zondervan.  There'll be a special Friday night session for youth and youth
    ministers &amp; sponsors, too, with Robin Johnson and the AUC (Alliance
    University College) Worship Band.
  </description>
</item>

<item>
  <title>
    Bonus Seminars -- Create a Volunteer Revolution
  </title>
  <link>http://www.trainconference.com/conference.html#volunteerRevolution</link>
  <category>Christian conferences</category>
  <pubDate>Sun, 31 Aug 2005 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
  <description>
    We are pleased to be able to partner this year with The Leadership Centre
    Willow Creek Canada to offer TRAIN 2005 registrants a bonus day on Friday
    at the Creating A Volunteer Revolution conference at no additional cost.
    One of the biggest needs expressed by church leaders is for more committed
    volunteers.  Even more important, your people long to have eternal
    significance.  That's why it's time for a revolution... one that helps you
    envision, empower and deploy every Christ-follower in your church to get
    off the sidelines and walk into the work of God's world-changing Kingdom!
  </description>
</item>

<item>
  <title>
    Registration Information
  </title>
  <link>http://www.trainconference.com/registration.html</link>
  <category>Christian conferences</category>
  <pubDate>Sun, 31 Aug 2005 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
  <description>
    Register for the TRAIN 2005 Conference using either the online or mail-in
    registration forms.  Walk-in registrations will also be accepted, though
    some seminars may be full by then.  A detailed fee schedule is available,
    as well as a list of nearby hotels for out out-of-town guests.
  </description>
</item>

<item>
  <title>
    The TRAIN 2005 Conference is Now Over -- See You in 2006!
  </title>
  <link>http://www.trainconference.com/</link>
  <category>Christian conferences</category>
  <pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2005 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
  <description>
    The TRAIN 2005 Conference is now over.  We trust and pray that you found
    encouragement in the Lord, and that you will continue to stand firm in your
    faith, to speak boldly to those around you, and to serve faithfully where
    the Spirit has led you to.  We look forward to doing more for you in 2006.
    The TRAIN 2006 Conference will be held November 3 &amp; 4, 2006.
  </description>
</item>

</channel>

</rss>